Last time on Zombieland Saga Revenge, we somehow got back into doing the idol thing.
It started with a TV appearance where we co-hosted a segment with Saga's very own rock star, White Ryu.
Can you believe?
Saki is a longtime fan of his, so she kind of went nuts.
It might even be love. Oh my gosh!
Then Saki found out that Ryu's radio show might be ending, and she went even more nuts!
She confessed her feelings to him, and he opened up to her, too.
It was super touching!
And now Frank Shishu is in charge of his radio show, so Saga can be Saga!
We're gonna light the way for Saga's burning soul!
Such super tight choreography.
We're probably not at that level.
I think Kotaro's getting out of the bath now, so...
What's wrong?
There's nothing wrong at all!
I'm done!
So what kind of stuff were you looking up?
Just random things.
Hey, don't eat that!
It's not a thing!
That's for...
Crap time!
Drop it!
We're already exactly right.
Those people...
Whatever I say!
Why would you be thinking about this hair?
Something that she likes talking about?
Things that usually look pretty tough, nobody does.
They would not have seen one thought.
But what kind of stuff that you tell people the first thought is?
What kind of stuff do you try to do?
A show at 6-5-6, and we're on the radio!
We hope you'll be there.
Thank you.
It feels like we're starting to make real progress.
The schedule sure is filling up, huh?
Half of these dates are for our part-time jobs, but yeah.
Hell, if we're paying off our debt and doing idle stuff at the same time, we're on our way to Easy Street.
Nope, not even close.
If we start thinking we can relax now, then all we'll ever be known for is the time we bombed.
We need to put the past behind us, find a way to rise above everyone's expectations.
And if we can't, then we might as well be dead and buried.
She's got a point. The entertainment industry's always been a cutthroat competition.
And to fall behind is to die.
I can't say no to a challenge.
Right, let's advance.
Better count me and two!
Come on, Ty!
I's exactly right.
We have to keep growing and moving forward.
Thank you for supporting the group!
Number three is so inspirational!
Yeah, you can tell she puts her all into it!
Question.
Which one looks better?
Watch.
Arm pointed out to the side or kind of downward?
Real quick.
I put together the intro for tomorrow's show.
Could you look it over for me?
I can't decide which one of these hair pieces would make me cuter!
Let me see here.
Either, both, doesn't matter.
Ai, can you please tell me what to do?
Ai, can I ask you for something?
Ai, do you have just a second?
Ai, help!
Ah!
Sakura center.
Junko and Lily, you'll be on the right side.
And Saki and Yugiri, you go on the left.
Back a bit more.
Iron Frill is coming here.
So get your zombie butts in here.
Let's go!
It's a raid!
An ambush!
They're coming!
You little guy!
Inai!
You are to respond with a sir, yes, sir!
You're just a bunch of wet corpses wallowing around in muck!
No, you're the maggots that ate the corpses!
Would you calm down?
Get back to Iron Frill.
Get the shit out of your ears and listen up, you shamble and sacks of bones!
There's about to be another landmark added to the fierce battlefield that is Saga.
The new Saga Arena!
Wait, the what now?
And guess who's breaking it in first?
Iron Frill, obviously!
Huh?
Now, why is a big-time idol group from Tokyo being brought in for the inaugural performance
at a venue in Little Old Saga, you may ask?
And to that I say, who freaking knows?
The important takeaway is that I found a way to weasel you maggots in as the opening air!
You and those are going to be so awesome that those Tokyo are going to leave here not to shame!
It's the perfect plan!
So memorize it!
You're kidding!
The Iron Frill?
Good!
We can handle this!
I know it!
You're right!
Yeah, lovely parade and all, but here comes the rain.
Number three's not performing.
What?
Why?
Oh?
Did all your brains finally leak out?
Iron Frill's famously deceased leader wants to flaunt her undeadliness right in front of
her old group?
We've been up in Saga's grill for months and we never worried about getting recognized before!
Yeah, and we performed in the same stage as them back at Saga Rock!
Please, we can't go on without Ai after coming this far!
Froschuchu isn't Froschuchu if we're not singing together!
Respect my authority or you'll run laps till your legs fall off again!
As for you, we've got some solo gigs lined up.
You'll be starting first thing tomorrow.
At least!
That didn't go too well.
So what now?
There's no reasoning with that guy.
I'm sure one of us would have had to sit out eventually due to an injury or something like that.
Maybe this is an opportunity for each member of Froschuchu to get a bit stronger.
But it'll make me sad if you're the only person who's left out!
Well, it's just this once.
We want revenge, right?
So we'll do whatever it takes to get it.
Junko?
I'm counting on you to take charge.
After me, you're the most experienced idol we've got.
Ugh.
Right!
All right!
Today's special guest is number three from Froschuchu!
Yay!
Woo!
Hey!
I'm so happy to be here!
Huh?
I guess number three's doing solo stuff these days.
I hope she's not breaking away from the gang.
So I have to ask, has anyone ever told you that you bear a striking resemblance to the late Ai Mizuno from Iron Thrill?
Yes, I do get that from time to time, actually.
She was a legendary idol who people still admire.
So I always consider it a compliment.
They want you in Fukuoka for a live event, plus the Nagasaki Hydrangea Festival, and Beppu Hot Springs Hell, too.
Now let me see here.
Why don't you take those offers and shove them up, you buds?
What were you doing?
Froschuchu was created for Saga and Saga alone.
Anyone else who wants you is merely trying to capitalize on Saga's glory.
So trust no one.
I've never heard you say that before.
Are you plotting something?
Why would you want to split us up at such an important time?
We can't afford to fail this next performance.
Just think about it.
If it turns out like EFS did.
Oh, honey, Froschuchu can get along perfectly well without you.
Besides, you left Junko in charge, right?
What's wrong?
You don't trust her?
Junko made it as a solo idol back in the 80s, when that was almost impossible to do.
And they've all been working so hard to get over the EFS disaster.
I'm sure that they can pull through.
It sounds like to me everything's pagey!
So if you just unclench your undead job for five minutes to focus on your solo career, and paying off this debt, we'd live happily ever after!
How am I supposed to do any of that if you keep on turning down offers for dumb reasons?
Everyone's been working so hard to learn the new choreo.
But we're nowhere near the level we should be if we want to impress the fans coming to see Iron Frill.
We just have to push ourselves.
The concert will be here before we know it.
If we don't nail this performance, we're going to bomb again!
Junko?
Uh, Junko?
Uh...
Did we do better that time?
I feel like we're still a little too stiff in some parts.
We should definitely go over it a couple more times, but you guys are doing a great job.
Hell yeah! Rock!
You just stared at us all creepy with your mouth open, so I wasn't sure how you felt about it.
This concert is a big deal for Franshu Shuu!
We've got this, man! We've got this by the ass!
Let's focus on one thing at a time before we start getting too excited, okay, ladies?
Yeah, I keep flailing my arms too much, and it's knocking my mic loose.
That's because you're forgetting the choreo and making up your own dance moves.
You seem troubled by something.
I don't think you should be doing this right now.
I'm so sorry, sir!
Maybe you should call it a day.
I'm back!
Oh, hey there, Tai.
Is everyone else still off at work?
Up next is Franshu Shuu's number three singing Awaken Returner.
If she'd been alive during my time in the 80s, I bet she could have become a top idol, maybe even as a solo artist.
I have got to get out of this funk.
Would you like to share your thoughts on the Saga Arena concert that's coming up this weekend?
Of course! We think it's gonna be a super incredible show!
Your national tour has generated a lot of buzz. People call you the top idol queens. Do you think you live up to the hype?
I mean, it would be conceded to say we're the best idols, but we're trendsetters, so we have a responsibility to keep evolving musically.
Shuri!
Saga's a big deal to us, and we're gonna bring it on.
Iron Frill is gonna prove to everyone that we're one of a kind and beyond compare.
We're better than ever, so get ready to see an amazing performance.
Now that's a star right there. It seems like the top idols from Tokyo really know what they're doing, huh?
Isn't Franshu Shuu performing with them over at the new Saga Arena?
Yeah, they're the opening act. It'd be amazing if they managed to outperform Iron Frill.
I wouldn't place bets on that happening.
Hold on, did she just say they're one of a kind and beyond compare?
So she's basically insulting the opening act as a declaration of war!
I'll make her choke on those words!
Kinda doubt she knows us.
Iron Frill is an absurdly famous idol group. It's natural for them to be confident.
If Iron Frill brings their A-game as promised, and if they perform on another level,
people will think we're nothing more than third-rate wannabes, and we'll never be able to get our revenge.
This is how you type.
That's not right!
What do I do?
Sorry, guys. I had to work late today, and...
this is how they feel better.
So, I dream time...
Go!
Saga!
Did you like that?
Did I like what?
I thought our routine could use a little something extra
so we can go out with a bang at the Saga Arena.
Junko, check it out!
Even Tai's getting into the groove.
Whoa, okay, but
we should probably be focusing on the song and dance moves first.
Yeah, of course we'll do that too.
But there's not a whole lot of time left before the concert,
so we thought we'd try something fresh
to leave a big impression on the audience.
It's bad enough without I being here,
so we gotta dig ourselves out of this grave
or we'll have another disaster on our hands.
What's wrong?
Does the routine need something extra?
It's not that exactly.
Awesome, so you want in on this party?
I just need some more time to think about it.
You do that.
Okay, well try it again,
but this time do it way louder.
Yeah!
I'm gonna shake these maracas like there's new tomorrow!
That's the spirit!
I'll do it too much!
I lost my Father'sви.
I know I can't believe in the money that I'm part of the night Thinkina.
Will you return to what?
That's it, you're asking.
Please respond.
There was an absolute love back home.
They were amorized she started dark.
NURURUR 박물
Joongko, that was beautiful!
Did you write-
Ugh-
AHHHHHH!
Oh… no
Ugh
I've heard that song used in a bunch of commercials before, but I didn't know it was one of yours.
Mm-hmm. It was the first one of my songs that managed to reach the top of the charts.
It kept growing in popularity, and before long, everyone knew the name Junko Kono.
I like to sing it when I'm trying to cheer myself up.
I'm so sorry, Junko.
Huh?
I think maybe we're all in a state of panic right now. We're just too focused on having an impact.
Agreed. I feel the same way. We're all having anxiety about this show, but I thought it was only me that was feeling it.
I love being a part of this group, and I want us to put on a great performance at the Saga Arena.
It's just, I'm so used to doing my own thing. Performing as a solo idol, you know?
Performing with others is a totally different experience. You have to stand out and blend in at the same time.
On top of that, I'm feeling everybody as a substitute idol leader.
Not true!
I happen to like your teaching methods because they're easy to understand, and you're super considerate of all of us.
You've schooled us on what it takes to be real idols.
You think so?
Let's talk to Ai about this. She might have some good advice, even if she won't be able to be on stage with us.
I know she's gone, but Kotaro never said we couldn't reach out to her.
You're right.
We'll tell her about our new ideas, and then we can pick her brain for some keen insight.
You're Fran Shishu's number three, right?
And you're from Mayan Frill.
Wow, you really do look like her.
Hold on, is that Ai?
And isn't that...
I've been keeping a close eye on Fran Shishu for a good while now, so I know what happened at the EFS show.
But you've been doing solo gigs lately.
I guess you've finally figured it out.
What do you mean by that?
Just drop the dumb act.
You know you're more talented than those other girls are.
I can tell by the way that you perform.
You would rather be a part of a group as good as Iron Frill.
I mean, why wouldn't you want to be?
We're the ultimate.
The top idol queens.
You may not want to admit it, but I see right through you.
Because I was also in a similar situation.
Ai Mizuno was an absolute legend as number one.
It hasn't been easy, but I've done everything in my power to shine brighter than she ever had the chance to.
I'm just...
Listen up, number three.
You should join Iron Frill.
I think you've got what it takes.
And you'll be doing yourself a disservice if you don't leave a backwards place like Saga soon.
You know Iron Frill is unbeatable.
Plus, we have the talent and the determination to stay on top, too.
You belong with our group, Ai.
You're leagues ahead of Fran Shishu.
Just think about it, okay?
We'll talk again after the show this weekend.
But you'll see.
Once you get a real taste of what we can do on stage, it'll be clear who the better group is.
Oh, my God.
It's me, Junko. Is someone better off with another team if it meant that they could shine a little bit brighter?
Next time on Zombieland Saga Revenge, Episode 4, Pure-Hearted Electric Saga. Be there.